zestair.com.ph 2009-12-16

# Zest Airways Inc. - Privacy Policy

We thank you for visiting our Web site and consider your privacy seriously. Please read through this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information to us. We encourage you to review the privacy policy set forth below whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Our privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. Please note that the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this Web site only and do not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to people that we do not employ or manage.

We collect and use personally identifiable information, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, birthday, gender, personal interests, occupation etc., when you voluntarily register for a Zest Air account or use our web pages, products and services. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request for certain products and services, to contact you about specials and new products, to assist us in customizing and improving the contents you see in our Web site, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, e.g. to include you to one of our mailing lists.

Our site uses cookie and tracking technology useful for gathering information about how our Web site is used, such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site.

We will not sell nor rent your personally identifiable information to other companies or people. However, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may only do so if and when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. We will not provide your personally identifiable information to other companies for marketing purposes.

Your Zest Air Account Information is kept well secure and is password protected We give you the ability to edit your Zest Air Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about specials and new products. Likewise, all emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings, if preferred.

We reserve the right to make changes to and amend this policy from time to time. Any substantial changes to this policy will be posted on our pages accordingly.

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us.
